<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
     xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
     xsi:schemaLocation="http://hl7.org/fhir ../../src-generated/schemas/fhir-single.xsd"
     xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
     lang="en">
  
  <a name="scope">  </a>

  
  <blockquote class="stu-note">
  This implementation guide and set of artifacts are still undergoing development.
  Content is for demonstration purposes only.
  </blockquote>

  
  <h3>Summary</h3>  <a name="summary"> </a>
    This implementation guide includes a DRFAFT machine-readable representation of WHO guidelines for Surveillance and Outbreak Toolkit. This implementation guide explicitly encodes data models, forms, terminologies, and data extractions, in a computable language to support implementation of case based surveillance use cases by WHO Member States.

    The guide is part of the <a href="https://www.who.int/teams/digital-health-and-innovation/smart-guidelines">WHO SMART Guidelines approach</a> to support countries to integrate WHO global health and data recommendations into digital systems accurately and consistently. 

<!-- BEGIN SECTION TO REMOVE WHEN CREATING A NEW GUIDE-->
  <h3>About this implementation guide=</h3> <a name="guide"> </a>
   This implementation guide is broken into the following levels of [knowledge representation](https://hl7.org/fhir/uv/cpg/documentation-approach-06-01-levels-of-knowledge-representation.html):
    <a href="index.html">Home</a> - contains references to the guidance, guidelines, policies and recommendations underpinning this implementation guide.
    <a href="business-requirements.html">Business Requirements</a> - contains the requirements for this implementation guide including the definition of key concepts, use cases, and a data dictionary.      
    <a href="data-models-and-exchange.html">Data Models and Exchange</a> - contains the data models and data exchange protocols with actors and transactions defined.
    <a href="deployment.html">Deployment Guidance </a> - contains relevant technical specifications and guidance, testing resources, reference implementation materials, and supporting guidance for adaptation to local contexts.
  

<!-- END SECTION TO REMOVE WHEN CREATING A NEW GUIDE-->
  
  <h3>References</h3>  <a name="references"> </a>
  This Implementation Guide is based on the following <a href="references.html">References</a>

  <h3>Dependencies</h3>  <a name="dependencies"> </a>
  {% include dependencies.xml %}
  
  <h3>Providing Feedback</h3>  <a name="feedback"> </a>
  {% include feedback.xml %}

  <h3>Disclaimer</h3>  <a name="disclaimer"> </a>
  {% include disclaimer.xml %}
</div>  
